Finding Aid for the Kendall Carly Browne Scripts PASC.0232
UCLA Library Special Collections
Kendall Carly Browne scripts
circa 1960s-circa 1970s
UCLA Library Special Collections
Browne, Kendall Carly
PASC.0232
0.75 Linear Feet (2 boxes)
Kendall Carly Browne, also known as KC Browne, was an actress. The collection consists of scripts related to her career.
Restrictions on Access
Open for research. All requests to access special collections materials must be made in advance using the request button located on this page.
Provenance/Source of Acquisition
Gift of K.C. Browne, 1983.
UCLA Catalog Record ID
UCLA Catalog Record ID: 9946589483606533
Biography
There is very little biographical information available about Kendall Carly Browne. She was married to producer Her Braverman and was the mother of Bart Braverman. The actress' credits include The Ed Wynn Show and a small number lesser known projects such as I Wonder Who's Killing Her Now?, Fear City, and Dreamscape. More recent credits include the television dramas CSI: Crime Scene Investigation and ER.
Scope and Content
The collection consists of scripts related to the career of actress, Kendall Carly Browne. The scripts appear to be for stage projects. Notably missing from the collection are scripts from many of the television and motion picture projects in which she was involved.
Organization and Arrangement
The scripts are arranged alphabetically by project title.
Actresses -- United States -- Archives.; Browne, Kendall Carly--Archives.
- America's Discovery: Mona Columbus, no date (Box 1, Folder 13)
  General note
  Miscellaneous monologue written by Marc Havoc.
- Another Waltz, no date (Box 1, Folder 2)
  First draft script.
- Another Waltz For Miss Teaporten, no date (Box 1, Folder 12)
  Script written by Susan Alcott and Marc Havoc.
- Can you hear me?, no date (Box 1, Folder 20)
  Script written by Dean Marc Norton.
- Crucible (The): Act Three, 1980 Nov 3 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  Script written by Arthur Miller.
- Eagle And The Butterfly (The), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  Script written by Mary Moline and Wayne Barnes.
- Good Heavens, no date (Box 1, Folder 16)
  Script written by Mary Moline.
- Halloween, no date (Box 1, Folder 6)
  Script.
- I Wanna Be Loved By You, 1968 May 21 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Script, written by Warren Miller.
- Movie Lovers (The), no date (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Script written by Terence Kingsley-Smith.
- Myrtle and Murphy, no date (Box 1, Folder 14)
  Script written by Marc Havoc.
- Number You Have Reached Has Been...(The), no date (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Story synopsis written by Marc Havoc.
- Old Dolls From Porjes, no date (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Palm Sunday, 1972 June 25 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  Second draft script.
- Palm Sunday, 1972 Sep 25 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Third draft script.
- Paper God, no date (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Paper God, no date (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Picnic On The Precipice, no date (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Princess of the Neon Times, no date (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Princess of the Neon Times, no date (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Quiet Please, There's An Actor On Stage, no date (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Say Goodbye to Julia Pastrana, no date (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Script written by Mark Havoc.
- Say Goodbye To Julia Pastrana, no date (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Today Is Independence Day, no date (Box 1, Folder 10)
  Script written by William Hanley.
- Unidentified play pages (photocopies), no date (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Unidentified script, no date (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Unidentified script, no date (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Unidentified script pages, no date (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Unidentified script pages, no date (Box 1, Folder 11)
- What Kind Of Car Was That?, no date (Box 1, Folder 24)
  Primary treatment written by Mary Moline.